Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪Blossoms rise and scatter never to return♪
♪تزهر الأزهار وتنتشر دون أن تعود♪
♪Time rushes on toward its withering end♪
♪الوقت يتسارع نحو نهايته الذابلة♪
♪Rights and wrongs unfold♪
♪الصواب والخطأ يتكشفان♪
♪Breaking through fate's tightening walls♪
♪اختراق جدران القدر المشددة♪
♪Few ever find their way home♪
♪قليلون هم من يجدون طريقهم إلى المنزل♪
♪Through storms and drifting snow as silver hair falls♪
♪من خلال العواصف والثلوج المتساقطة بينما يتساقط الشعر الفضي♪
♪A lifetime of ruin for one bitter revel♪
♪حياة من الخراب من أجل احتفال مرير واحد♪
♪A single dream born from a single thought♪
♪حلم واحد ولد من فكرة واحدة♪
♪Shattered at a touch♪
♪تحطم عند لمسة♪
♪When the dream fades I look once more♪
♪عندما يتلاشى الحلم أنظر مرة أخرى♪
=Aligned Reverence=
=الاحترام المتوافق=
(Adapted from Jinyi's novel of the same name on Qimao Novel)
(مقتبس من رواية جيني التي تحمل نفس الاسم على Qimao Novel)
=Episode 1= (Why are you running?)
=الحلقة 1= (لماذا تركض؟)
(Lu Zhuo)
(لو تشو)
(Lady Yuan of the Su family, Su Jinyuan)
(السيدة يوان من عائلة سو، سو جينيوان)
Lady Yuan.
السيدة يوان.
You abandoned the Xiao family to run away with me.
لقد تركت عائلة شياو لتهرب معي.
In this life, I, Lu Zhuo,
في هذه الحياة، أنا، لو تشو،
will never fail you.
لن يخذلك أبدًا.
Lu Zhuo.
لو تشو.
This moment
هذه اللحظة
is exactly as it was
هو بالضبط كما كان
in our past life.
في حياتنا الماضية.
What?
ماذا؟
In our past life, you taught me how to read the human heart.
في حياتنا الماضية، علمتني كيفية قراءة القلب البشري.
In this life,
في هذه الحياة،
I will send you to hell!
سأرسلك إلى الجحيم!
Run! The Xiao family's adopted son Xie Yunyan has rebelled!
اهرب! لقد تمرد شي يونيان، الابن المتبنى لعائلة شياو !
They are about to break into the imperial city!
إنهم على وشك اقتحام المدينة الإمبراطورية!
Run!
يجري!
Go!
يذهب!
Move!
يتحرك!
Still thinking about the Xiao family?
هل لازلت تفكر في عائلة شياو؟
They colluded with the enemy and betrayed the realm!
تواطؤوا مع العدو وخانوا المملكة!
They were wiped out. Understand?
لقد تم القضاء عليهم. هل فهمت؟
Go!
يذهب!
Are you going or not?
هل انت ذاهب ام لا؟
It is useless.
إنه عديم الفائدة.
You still cannot bear to leave?
هل لا تزال لا تستطيع أن تتحمل الرحيل؟
Still reluctant to go?
هل لا تزال متردد في الذهاب؟
(The Xiao family's adopted son, Xie Yunyan)
(الابن المتبنى لعائلة شياو، شيه يونيان)
Lady Yuan of the Su family.
السيدة يوان من عائلة سو.
Xie Yunyan.
شيه يونيان.
Back then, you ran away with this adulterer.
في ذلك الوقت، هربت مع هذا الزاني.
My elder brother lost all honor.
لقد فقد أخي الأكبر كل شرفه.
You made the Xiao family a laughingstock.
لقد جعلت عائلة شياو أضحوكة.
I ask you to judge fairly.
أطلب منكم الحكم بالعدل.
I...
أنا...
I was tempted by this faithless woman.
لقد أغريت بهذه المرأة الخائنة.
Lu Zhuo.
لو تشو.
You clearly vowed we would stay true to each other.
لقد أقسمت بوضوح أننا سنبقى صادقين مع بعضنا البعض.
That was why I...
لهذا السبب أنا...
Shut up!
اسكت!
Those who betray the Xiao family
أولئك الذين خانوا عائلة شياو
must die.
يجب أن يموت.
Sir.
سيد.
Sir, look.
سيدي، انظر.
I have already killed this wretch.
لقد قتلت هذا الوغد بالفعل.
Will you not spare me?
هل لن تدخر لي؟
To think you would
أعتقد أنك سوف
betray the Xiao family for such a faithless creature.
خيانة عائلة شياو من أجل مثل هذا المخلوق الخائن.
Enough.
كافٍ.
Go to the underworld
اذهب إلى العالم السفلي
and answer for what you owe the Xiao family.
والإجابة على ما تدين به لعائلة شياو.
Slaughter every treacherous court official
اذبحوا كل مسؤول محكمة خائن
in honor of the Xiao family's fallen heroes.
تكريما لأبطال عائلة شياو الذين سقطوا.
Slaughter every treacherous court official
اذبحوا كل مسؤول محكمة خائن
in honor of the Xiao family's fallen heroes.
تكريما لأبطال عائلة شياو الذين سقطوا.
You...
أنت...
You are mad.
أنت مجنون.
You used news of my brother
لقد استخدمت أخبار أخي
to trick me into fleeing the marriage.
لخداعي للهروب من الزواج.
You used the name of a first wife
لقد استخدمت اسم الزوجة الأولى
to make me give you my whole heart.
لتجعلني أعطيك قلبي كله.
You deceived me,
لقد خدعتني
humiliated me,
أذلني،
trampled on me,
داس عليّ
and you even want to kill me.
وأنت تريد أن تقتلني.
The one who truly deserves death
من يستحق الموت حقا
is you!
هو انت!
(What belonged to the past life)
(ما كان من الحياة الماضية)
(has turned to dust.)
(تحول إلى غبار.)
(In this life,)
(في هذه الحياة)
(I will become a completely new Su Jinyuan.)
(سوف أصبح Su Jinyuan جديدًا تمامًا.)
Is anyone there?
هل هناك أحد؟
Please help me.
من فضلك ساعدني.
(Xie Yunyan?)
(شيه يونيان؟)
Those who betray the Xiao family
أولئك الذين خانوا عائلة شياو
must die.
يجب أن يموت.
Lady Yuan of the Su family.
السيدة يوان من عائلة سو.
The fire at the ancient temple
حريق المعبد القديم
was your doing.
كان هذا من فعلك.
I know you intend to kill me.
أعلم أنك تنوي قتلي.
Save your strength.
أحفظ قوتك
You would throw your life away just to escape this marriage.
سوف تتخلص من حياتك فقط من أجل الهروب من هذا الزواج.
I did not escape.
لم أهرب.
Lu Zhuo deceived me.
لقد خدعني لو تشو.
He told me there was news of my missing brother.
أخبرني أن هناك أخبارًا عن اختفاء أخي.
That was why I left the city with him.
ولهذا السبب غادرت المدينة معه.
In the end,
في النهاية،
I was the one who wronged the Xiao family.
أنا من ظلم عائلة شياو.
Shall I then help you, Young Lady Su,
هل يمكنني مساعدتك إذن، أيتها السيدة الشابة سو،
drag Lu Zhuo here,
اسحب لو تشو هنا،
skin him,
سلخه
grind his bones,
طحن عظامه،
and make him atone to you?
وتجعله يكفر عنك؟
That is my own matter.
هذا أمر خاص بي.
It does not concern you.
لا يهمك .
Even now
حتى الآن
you still defend that adulterer?
هل مازلت تدافع عن هذا الزاني؟
I am not.
انا لست كذلك.
Come back to the Xiao family with me.
عودوا معي إلى عائلة شياو.
Before the ancestral hall,
أمام القاعة الأجدادية،
you will explain everything yourself.
سوف تشرح كل شيء بنفسك.
(Three months after the wedding in the past life,)
(بعد ثلاثة أشهر من الزواج في الحياة الماضية)
(the Xiao father and son were defeated at Linchuan,)
( هُزم الأب والابن شياو في لينتشوان)
(and were executed for treason along with the entire clan.)
(وتم إعدامهم بتهمة الخيانة مع العشيرة بأكملها.)
(Years later, Xie Yunyan raised troops in rebellion.)
(بعد سنوات، قام شي يون يان بحشد القوات للتمرد.)
(If follows him home,)
(إذا تبعه إلى المنزل)
(it would be walking toward death once more.)
(سيكون ذلك بمثابة السير نحو الموت مرة أخرى.)
I cannot go back.
لا أستطيع العودة.
You...
أنت...
Young master.
سيد شاب.
The wolves may return at any moment.
قد تعود الذئاب في أي لحظة.
(Xiang Lei) We must leave quickly.
(شيانغ لي) يجب علينا المغادرة بسرعة.
Very well.
جيد جدا.
Once the wolves have stripped the flesh from your bones,
بمجرد أن يقوم الذئاب بتجريد اللحم من عظامك،
I will carry your remains back.
سأحمل رفاتك مرة أخرى.
It makes no difference.
لا يوجد فرق.
Spit it out.
ابصقه.
Are you trying to die?
هل تحاول أن تموت؟
I will not die.
لن أموت.
I will live
سأعيش
better than anyone else.
أفضل من أي شخص آخر.
What did you ever see in him?
ماذا رأيت فيه على الإطلاق؟
Xiao family holds the title of Duke who guards the realm.
عائلة شياو تحمل لقب الدوق الذي يحرس المملكة.
My elder brother is gentle and valiant.
أخي الأكبر لطيف وشجاع.
Yet you fled the marriage
ولكنك هربت من الزواج
for a man who could not even feed you properly.
لرجل لم يستطع حتى أن يطعمك بشكل صحيح.
I wronged the Xiao family.
لقد ظلمت عائلة شياو.
I was blind.
لقد كنت أعمى.
Why are you crying?
لماذا تبكي؟
Because you fled the marriage,
لأنك هربت من الزواج،
my elder brother suffered mockery and blame.
لقد عانى أخي الأكبر من السخرية واللوم.
Even when he was urgently summoned to war,
حتى عندما تم استدعاؤه للحرب بشكل عاجل،
he still wanted to shield you.
مازال يريد حمايتك.
He told others you fell gravely ill,
لقد أخبر الآخرين أنك مرضت مرضًا خطيرًا،
and sent me to look for you in secret.
وأرسلني للبحث عنك سراً.
(Why was the campaign moved ahead?)
(لماذا تم المضي قدماً في الحملة؟)
Then I truly cannot return.
إذن لن أستطيع العودة حقا.
You keep saying you wronged the Xiao family,
تستمر في القول بأنك ظلمتَ عائلة شياو،
so why will you not go back?
فلماذا لا تعود؟
If I told you
لو قلت لك
that disaster will soon fall on the Xiao family,
أن الكارثة ستقع قريبا على عائلة شياو،
would you believe me?
هل ستصدقني؟
Xie Yunyan.
شيه يونيان.
♪Even the gentlest waves can never be your touch♪
♪حتى الأمواج الأكثر لطفًا لا يمكنها أبدًا أن تصل إلى لمستك♪
♪No lighthouse waiting ever matched the way I held on♪
♪لم يسبق أن قارنا بين منارة الانتظار والطريقة التي تمسكت بها♪
♪The harbor lies in silent moonlight♪
♪الميناء يقع في ضوء القمر الصامت♪
♪The pipes call no seabirds home♪
♪الأنابيب لا تدعو الطيور البحرية إلى المنزل♪
♪This coastal line feels barren as a wasteland♪
♪يبدو هذا الخط الساحلي قاحلًا كأرض قاحلة♪
♪They laugh at those who carve their hopes into drifting boats♪
♪إنهم يضحكون على أولئك الذين ينحتون آمالهم في قوارب عائمة♪
♪Yet in my loneliest nights you never reached for me♪
♪ولكن في ليالي الوحدة لم تقترب مني أبدًا♪
♪At the far edge of the tides I waited long for you♪
♪في أقصى حافة المد والجزر انتظرتك طويلاً♪
♪Seasons washed away by ebb and flow but still I never left♪
♪مرت الفصول بالمد والجزر ولكنني لم أغادر أبدًا♪
♪A gentle breeze slips through mirage and illusion♪
♪نسيمة لطيفة تتسلل عبر السراب والوهم♪
♪Even starlight's tender message pales beside your single greeting♪
♪حتى رسالة ضوء النجوم الرقيقة تتضاءل أمام تحيتك الوحيدة♪
♪At the far edge of the tides I waited long for you♪
♪في أقصى حافة المد والجزر انتظرتك طويلاً♪
♪Longing lets the monsoon wrinkle time as I run to you♪
♪الشوق يجعل الرياح الموسمية تتجعد الوقت وأنا أركض إليك♪
♪Snow may turn one's hair to white yet I burn all bridges for you♪
♪قد يحوّل الثلج شعر الإنسان إلى اللون الأبيض، ولكنني أحرق كل الجسور من أجلك♪
♪When the sea calms after the storm I will see you turning back♪
♪عندما يهدأ البحر بعد العاصفة سأراك تعود ♪
♪At the far edge of the tides I waited long for you♪
♪في أقصى حافة المد والجزر انتظرتك طويلاً♪
♪Seasons washed away by ebb and flow but still I never left♪
♪مرت الفصول بالمد والجزر ولكنني لم أغادر أبدًا♪
♪A gentle breeze slips through mirage and illusion♪
♪نسيمة لطيفة تتسلل عبر السراب والوهم♪
♪When the sea calms after the storm I will see you turning back♪
♪عندما يهدأ البحر بعد العاصفة سأراك تعود ♪